Subject Files
Marist Archives and Special Collections
- Subject Files, 2.1.3.6
  - Subject files: Pan America flight (United States Army), 1926 - 1927; 6 (Box 1551)
    - Presentation of Distinguished Flying Crosses at Pan-American Union by Sec. War, 1
    - Verso: Presentation of Distinguished Flying Crosses at Pan-American Union by Sec. War, 1-verso
    - [Man standing with two Pan-American Flight pilots], 2
    - Langley Field, Maj. Dargue, 3
    - Verso: Langley Field, Maj. Dargue, 3-verso
    - Presentation of DSC P.A. Union Dec 21, 1927, 4
    - Verso: Presentation of DSC P.A. Union Dec 21, 1927, 4-verso
    - at Bolling Field May 2, 1927, 5
    - Verso: at Bolling Field May 2, 1927, 5-verso
    - Hearses carrying Woolsey + Benton at B.A., 6
    - Verso: Hearses carrying Woolsey + Benton at B.A., 6-verso
    - Capt. Wollsey + Lieut. Benton lying in state at Buenos Aries, 7
    - Verso: Capt. Wollsey + Lieut. Benton lying in state at Buenos Aries, 7-verso
    - [Parade (?) for the Pan-American Fliers], 8
    - [Two pilots of the Pan-American Flight standing in front of their plane, "Detroit"], 9
    - Army Flying Field 15 miles out of Rio, 10
    - Verso: Army Flying Field 15 miles out of Rio, 10-verso
    - U.S. Ambassador Morgan + P.A. Flyers at reception at Petropolis, summer home of President of Brazil, 11
    - Verso: U.S. Ambassador Morgan + P.A. Flyers at reception at Petropolis, summer home of President of Brazil, 11-verso
    - Reception + dance at Country Club Rio., 12
    - Verso: Reception + dance at Country Club Rio., 12-verso
    - Ilha do Govermenador, Noral Flying Field Rio [?], 13
    - Verso: Ilha do Govermenador, Noral Flying Field Rio [?], 13-verso
    - Rio, 14
    - Verso: Rio, 14-verso
    - Sao Paulo, Brazil, 15
    - Verso: Sao Paulo, Brazil, 15-verso
    - Sautos, Brazil, 16
    - Verso: Sautos, Brazil, 16-verso
    - Porto Allegre - Brazil, 17
    - Verso: Porto Allegre - Brazil, 17-verso
    - Florianapolis - Brazil, 18
    - Verso: Florianapolis - Brazil, 18-verso
    - The San Francisco almost goes on the rocks at Montevideo, 19
    - Verso: The San Francisco almost goes on the rocks at Montevideo, 19-verso
    - The San Francisco was nearly washed up on the rocks at Montevideo, 20
    - Verso: The San Francisco was nearly washed up on the rocks at Montevideo, 20-verso
    - Landing at Pocitos Beach, Montevideo, 21
    - Verso: Landing at Pocitos Beach, Montevideo, 21-verso
    - Pocitos Beach, Uruguay, 22
    - Verso: Pocitos Beach, Uruguay, 22-verso
    - On the beach at Montevideo, 23
    - Verso: On the beach at Montevideo, 23-verso
    - [Pan-American Flight plane in the water], 24
    - Lima, Peru; Left to right, Ambassador Poinclefter[?] (he took a ride in one of our planes), Capt. McDaniel, Lieut. H. R. Harris (formerly Air Corps, now with Pam-Am Airways), Mr. Bool, Secy of Embassy, 25
    - Verso: Lima, Peru; Left to right, Ambassador Poinclefter[?] (he took a ride in one of our planes), Capt. McDaniel, Lieut. H. R. Harris (formerly Air Corps, now with Pam-Am Airways), Mr. Bool, Secy of Embassy, 25-verso
    - [Aerial view of a harbor-THIS PICTURE NEEDS TO BE ROTATED ON THE FINDING AID], 26
    - At Montevideo, 27
    - Verso: At Montevideo, 27-verso
    - Pocitis Beach, Montevideo, 28
    - Verso: Pocitis Beach, Montevideo, 28-verso
    - Governor's palace - Victoria, Brazil, 29
    - Verso: Governor's palace - Victoria, Brazil, 29-verso
    - Caption: Entrance to Harbor - Natal, Brazil. Old Dutch Fort on reef, 30
    - Lunch at Victoria, Brazil. On the beach., 31
    - Verso: Lunch at Victoria, Brazil. On the beach., 31-verso
    - Victoria, Brazil, 32
    - Verso: Victoria, Brazil, 32-verso
    - Victoria, Brazil, 33
    - Verso: Victoria, Brazil, 33-verso
    - [First World Flight in Brazil], 34
    - We placed a wreath on the tomb of Bolivar. Caracas, Venez., 35
    - Verso: We placed a wreath on the tomb of Bolivar. Caracas, Venez., 35-verso
    - Caracas Ven. Dargue, Banquet at Military College, 36
    - Verso: Caracas Ven. Dargue, Banquet at Military College, 36-verso
    - Caracas Ven. Dargue, Military College, 37
    - Verso: Caracas Ven. Dargue, Military College, 37-verso
    - Cayenne, Fr. Guiana, 38
    - Verso: Cayenne, Fr. Guiana, 38-verso
    - Port of La guayre - Venezuela showing old fort on hill., 39
    - Verso: Port of La guayre - Venezuela showing old fort on hill., 39-verso
    - Fortress "El Castillo Liberator" and Navy Yard - Puerto Cabello - Venezuela, 40
    - Verso: Fortress "El Castillo Liberator" and Navy Yard - Puerto Cabello - Venezuela, 40-verso
    - Caracas, Venezuela, 41
    - Verso: Caracas, Venezuela, 41-verso
    - Caracas, Ven. Dargue, Our home while in the city Casa de Espana, 42
    - Verso: Caracas, Ven. Dargue, Our home while in the city Casa de Espana, 42-verso
  Box 1552
- Subject Files, 2.1.3.6
  - Subject files: Pan America flight (United States Army), 1926 - 1927; 1 (Box 1552)
    - A scene at the accident. B.A., 1
    - Verso: A scene at the accident. B.A., 1-verso
    - Wing of Detroit after being burned in accident at B.A., 2
    - Verso: Wing of Detroit after being burned in accident at B.A., 2-verso
    - The accident at B.A., 3
    - Verso: The accident at B.A., 3-verso
    - The burned wreak of the Detroit, 4
    - Verso: The burned wreak of the Detroit, 4-verso
    - Moonlight on the Guayas River, Ecuador, 5
    - Verso: Moonlight on the Guayas River, Ecuador, 5-verso
    - Agricultural School, Lima, 6
    - Verso: Agricultural School, Lima, 6-verso
    - Our escort to Las Polmas flying field - Lima, 7
    - Verso: Our escort to Las Polmas flying field - Lima, 7-verso
    - An Indian maiden with her knitting in Peru, 8
    - Verso: An Indian maiden with her knitting in Peru, 8-verso
    - Mayor of Arequipa, Peru, making us "Illustrious Guests" of the city, 9
    - Verso: Mayor of Arequipa, Peru, making us "Illustrious Guests" of the city, 9-verso
    - Mrs. Bates, out hostess at Quinto Bates, Arequipa, 10
    - Verso: Mrs. Bates, out hostess at Quinto Bates, Arequipa, 10-verso
    - Snow covered mountains back of Arequipa, Peru, 11
    - Verso: Snow covered mountains back of Arequipa, Peru, 11-verso
    - Going ashore at Mollendo, 12
    - Verso: Going ashore at Mollendo, 12-verso
    - Forced landing of New York at Guatemala City, 13
    - Verso: Forced landing of New York at Guatemala City, 13-verso
    - Citadel, Guatemala City, 14
    - Verso: Citadel, Guatemala City, 14-verso
    - Caption: Guatemala City, 15
    - Vera Cruz, 16
    - Verso: Vera Cruz, 16-verso
    - Ambassador + Mrs. Sheffield and staff at Mexico City Embassy., 17
    - Verso: Ambassador + Mrs. Sheffield and staff at Mexico City Embassy., 17-verso
    - Plaza + cathedral Mex City from airplane, 18
    - Verso: Plaza + cathedral Mex City from airplane, 18-verso
    - Pyramid of the Sun, Teotihuacan, Mexico, 19
    - Verso: Pyramid of the Sun, Teotihuacan, Mexico, 19-verso
    - Inner court of mansion in Mexico City built by Count of San Mateo of Valparaiso, 20
    - Verso: Inner court of mansion in Mexico City built by Count of San Mateo of Valparaiso, 20-verso
    - Tampico[?] Mexico shipping gas in cans, 21
    - Verso: Tampico[?] Mexico shipping gas in cans, 21-verso
    - The flight at Point Isabel, U.S. [on same sheet as 1.23], 22
    - Verso: The flight at Point Isabel, U.S., 22-verso
    - At San Antonio [on same sheet as 1.22], 23
    - Verso: At San Antonio, 23-verso
    - Point Isabel, Texas [on same sheet as 1.25], 24
    - Verso: Point Isabel, Texas, 24-verso
    - [Pan-American Flight planes lined up], [on same sheet as 1.24], 25
    - Capt. Woolsey, Mr. Grover Loening, First flight of the Pan American Ship. Oct. 26, 1926; Mrs. Woolsey, 35 S. Grand Ave. Osborn Ohio, 26
    - Verso: Capt. Woolsey, Mr. Grover Loening, First flight of the Pan American Ship. Oct. 26, 1926; Mrs. Woolsey, 35 S. Grand Ave. Osborn Ohio, 26-verso
    - Col. Monita[?] Jap Mil. Atl. Takes us all in at S.A. prior to departure, 27
    - Verso: Col. Monita[?] Jap Mil. Atl. Takes us all in at S.A. prior to departure, 27-verso
    - Mrs. Dargue with Major, 28
    - Verso: Mrs. Dargue with Major, 28-verso
    - LOENING AMPHIBIAN To be used on the Pan American Flight shown beside the BOSTON - Round-the-World-Crusier. Amphibian beside Boston, world flight cruiser, 29
    - Verso: LOENING AMPHIBIAN To be used on the Pan American Flight shown beside the BOSTON - Round-the-World-Crusier. Amphibian beside Boston, world flight cruiser, 29-verso
    - Charting the route, Maj. Dargue + Capt. Eabe[?], 30
    - Verso: Charting the route, Maj. Dargue + Capt. Eabe[?], 30-verso
    - [Portrait of an officer of the Pan-American Flight], 31
    - Caption: Clinton F. Woolsey, Capt Air Corps; Verso: Mrs. C. Woolsey 35 S. Grand Ave. Osborn Ohio, 32
    - Verso: Mrs. C. Woolsey 35 S. Grand Ave. Osborn Ohio, 32-verso
    - Indian playground, Peru, 33
    - Verso: Indian playground, Peru, 33-verso
    - Llamas in Peru, Mt. Misti., 34
    - Verso: Llamas in Peru, Mt. Misti., 34-verso
    - A minute or two before the fatal accident; Caption: Argentine[?], 35
    - Verso: A minute or two before the fatal accident, 35-verso
    - Coming up the ramp at Mar del Plata Argentina, 36
    - Verso: Coming up the ramp at Mar del Plata Argentina, 36-verso
    - Leaving the battleship after the reception at B/A, 37
    - Verso: Leaving the battleship after the reception at B/A, 37-verso
    - Greeted by the Admiral at the Naval Air Station, Puerto Belgrando, Argentina, after the flight across the Andes., 38
    - Verso: Greeted by the Admiral at the Naval Air Station, Puerto Belgrando, Argentina, after the flight across the Andes., 38-verso
    - Landing at B/A, 39
    - Verso: Landing at B/A, 39-verso
    - B/A, 40
    - Verso: B/A, 40-verso
    - Detroit's arrival at Mar del Plate. 5834 A.S. Left side of landing gear gave way., 41
    - Verso: Detroit's arrival at Mar del Plate. 5834 A.S. Left side of landing gear gave way., 41-verso
    - Indian Hut in mountains of Peru, 42
    - Verso: Indian Hut in mountains of Peru, 42-verso
    - Ready for refueling at Mejillones, 43
    - Verso: Ready for refueling at Mejillones, 43-verso
    - The New York coming ashore at Mejillones, 44
    - Verso: The New York coming ashore at Mejillones, 44-verso
    - The N.Y. 5835AS, 45
    - Verso: The N.Y. 5835AS, 45-verso
  - Subject files: Pan America flight (United States Army), 1926 - 1927; 2 (Box 1552)
    - Callao[?], 1
    - Verso: Callao[?], 1-verso
    - Paita, Peru, 2
    - Verso: Paita, Peru, 2-verso
    - [Lowell Thomas in flight suit], 3
    - [mounted photograph], [Religious building[?] with tower], 4
    - A pipe line running out through the rough water on the coast of Peru, 5
    - Verso: A pipe line running out through the rough water on the coast of Peru, 5-verso
    - In the back yard of our hotel at Paita, Peru, 6
    - Verso: In the back yard of our hotel at Paita, Peru, 6-verso
    - A call on[?] the President of Colombia at Bogota, 7
    - Verso: A call on[?] the President of Colombia at Bogota, 7-verso
    - Cartagena, 8
    - Verso: Cartagena, 8-verso
    - Maintenance work while standing in the water. Cartagena, Col., 9
    - Verso: Maintenance work while standing in the water. Cartagena, Col., 9-verso
    - Cartagena, Col., 10
    - Verso: Cartagena, Col., 10-verso
    - Port of Guayaquil, 11
    - Verso: Port of Guayaquil, 11-verso
    - Seasonal fruit market in the open air; Guayaquil, Ecuador, 12
    - Verso: Seasonal fruit market in the open air; Guayaquil, Ecuador, 12-verso
    - Guayaquil, Ecuador. Las Petras - The Venetian quarters of the city, 13
    - Verso: Guayaquil, Ecuador. Las Petras - The Venetian quarters of the city, 13-verso
    - Drying cocoa in Guayaquil, 14
    - Verso: Drying cocoa in Guayaquil, 14-verso
    - Caption: "Detroit" "San Francisco" "St. Louis"; "Pan American Flight" Passing Duarte Is. Enroute to Colombia, 15
    - Barrauquilla - Colombia-, 16
    - Verso: Barrauquilla - Colombia-, 16-verso
    - Caption: Off Pueeblo Neuvo going south from Panama City, R.P. "Pan American Flight", 17
    - Caption: Passing Gaillard Cut on the way to South America. "Pan American Flight", 18
    - Caption: The "New York" over Gatun Lake, C.Z. "Pan American Flight", 19
    - France Field, Colon[?], 20
    - Verso: France Field, Colon[?], 20-verso
    - Arrival of New York and St. Louis at Panama ahead of other 3 planes. Col. Fisher greeting Capt. Woolsey, 21
    - Verso: Arrival of New York and St. Louis at Panama ahead of other 3 planes. Col. Fisher greeting Capt. Woolsey, 21-verso
    - Caption: "Pan American Flight" At France Field, C.Z., 22
    - Caption: Going out of the line for the take off at France Field, C.Z. "Pan American Flight", 23
    - Caption: "Pan American Flight" At France Field, C.Z., 24
    - Caption: Getting ready for takeoff at France Field, C.Z. "Pan American Flight", 25
    - [Portrait of an officer involved with the Pan-American Flight], 26
    - [Portrait of an officer involved in the Pan-American Flight], 27
    - [Portrait of an officer involved in the Pan-American Flight], 28
    - [Portrait of an officer involved with the Pan-American Flight], 29
    - [Portrait of an officer involved in the Pan-American Flight], 30
    - [Portrait of an officer involved with the Pan-American Flight], 31
    - [Portrait of an officer involved in the Pan-American Flight], 32
    - Maj. Herbert A Dargue, 33
    - Verso: Maj. Herbert A Dargue, 33-verso
    - [Portrait of an officer involved in the Pan-American Flight], 34
    - Lake Ilopango, Landing Field, San Salvador., 35
    - Verso: Lake Ilopango, Landing Field, San Salvador., 35-verso
    - Verso: Lake Llapando [Ilopango?] with landing field near San Salvador, Salvador; Dargue, 36
    - Lake Llapando [Ilopango?] with landing field near San Salvador, Salvador; Dargue, 36-verso
    - Palacio Nacional De El Salvador in San Salvador, 37
    - Verso: Palacio Nacional De El Salvador in San Salvador, 37-verso
    - Amapala, Honduras, 38
    - Verso: Amapala, Honduras, 38-verso
    - Amapala, 39
    - Verso: Amapala, 39-verso
    - Presidential Palace and Bridge Mayol, 40
    - Verso: Presidential Palace and Bridge Mayol, 40-verso
    - Tegucigalpa, Honduras at the American legation Minister Summerlia[?] (white hair) President on his left, Secy. Way on his right, 41
    - Verso: Tegucigalpa, Honduras at the American legation Minister Summerlia[?] (white hair) President on his left, Secy. Way on his right, 41-verso
    - Brito, Nicaragua, 42
    - Verso: Brito, Nicaragua, 42-verso
    - Coseguina Volcano, Nicaragua, 43
    - Verso: Coseguina Volcano, Nicaragua, 43-verso
    - Asilo Chapin, San Jose, C.R., 44
    - Verso: Asilo Chapin, San Jose, C.R., 44-verso
    - Puntarenas, Costa Rica, 45
    - Verso: Puntarenas, Costa Rica, 45-verso
    - Landing Field, Managua, Nicaragua, 46
    - Verso: Landing Field, Managua, Nicaragua, 46-verso
    - Panama - view of Aucon[?] - Tivoli and part of Panama from Aucon Hill, 47
    - Verso: Panama - view of Aucon[?] - Tivoli and part of Panama from Aucon Hill, 47-verso
    - Pedregal, Panama, 48
    - Verso: Pedregal, Panama, 48-verso
  - Subject files: Pan America flight (United States Army), 1926 - 1927; 3 (Box 1552)
    - Reception at Country Club, Rio de Janiero, 1
    - Verso: Reception at Country Club, Rio de Janiero, 1-verso
    - Along the Daule River, Ecuador, 2
    - Verso: Along the Daule River, Ecuador, 2-verso
    - Porte Allegre - Rio Grande de Sul - Brazil, 3
    - Verso: Porte Allegre - Rio Grande de Sul - Brazil, 3-verso
    - Sao Paulo - Brazil, snake houses Butantau Institute, 4
    - Verso: Sao Paulo - Brazil, snake houses Butantau Institute, 4-verso
    - [People standing in a field; taken during the Pan-American Flight, 5
    - Caption: Seara River[?], 6
    - Fortaleza, Brazil, 7
    - Verso: Fortaleza, Brazil, 7-verso
    - Ceara River, Fortaleza, Brazil, 8
    - Verso: Ceara River, Fortaleza, Brazil, 8-verso
    - Naval Air Base, Florianopolis, Brazil, 9
    - Verso: Naval Air Base, Florianopolis, Brazil, 9-verso
    - San Jose, Guatemala, 10
    - Verso: San Jose, Guatemala, 10-verso
    - Ministaitan[?], 11
    - Verso: Ministaitan[?], 11-verso
    - LOENING AMPHIBIAN Airplane that will be used on the Pan American Flight shown here as a land plane. Note: The plane used will have a three-blade steel propeller., 12
    - Verso: LOENING AMPHIBIAN Airplane that will be used on the Pan American Flight shown here as a land plane. Note: The plane used will have a three-blade steel propeller., 12-verso
    - Landing Field, Anton, Panama, 13
    - Verso: Landing Field, Anton, Panama, 13-verso
    - Landing Field, Anton, Panama, 14
    - Verso: Landing Field, Anton, Panama, 14-verso
    - Landing Field, David, Panama, 15
    - Verso: Landing Field, David, Panama, 15-verso
    - David, Panama, 16
    - Verso: David, Panama, 16-verso
    - Albrook Field, Panama, 17
    - Verso: Albrook Field, Panama, 17-verso
    - Cow [Coco?] Solo Landing Field, Colon[?], 18
    - Verso: Cow [Coco?] Solo Landing Field, Colon[?], 18-verso
    - Am. Consul at Guayaquil, 19
    - Verso: Am. Consul at Guayaquil, 19-verso
    - Laguna Madre Santa Isabel, Tex, 20
    - Verso: Laguna Madre Santa Isabel, Tex, 20-verso
    - Luncheon by Sen Kellogg at P.A. Union, Wash. D.C. Nov 16, 1926, 21
    - Verso: Luncheon by Sen Kellogg at P.A. Union, Wash. D.C. Nov 16, 1926, 21-verso
    - Monument to Daniel Hernandez, San Salvador - Salvador, 22
    - Verso: Monument to Daniel Hernandez, San Salvador - Salvador, 22-verso
    - Wharf at La Libertad- Salvador, 23
    - Verso: Wharf at La Libertad- Salvador, 23-verso
    - Landing Field, Guatemala City, 24
    - Verso: Landing Field, Guatemala City, 24-verso
    - [Pan-American Flight plane], 25
    - [Pan-American Flight plane], 26
    - [Caption: Pan-American Flight], 27
    - A Coast line scene in Chile + Peru, 28
    - Verso: A Coast line scene in Chile + Peru, 28-verso
    - A pipe line (oil) to the coast of Peru, 29
    - Verso: A pipe line (oil) to the coast of Peru, 29-verso
  - Subject files: Pan America flight (United States Army), 1926 - 1927; 4 (Box 1552)
    - Caracas Ven, Dargue, At the reception Military [illegible], 1
    - Verso: Caracas Ven, Dargue, At the reception Military [illegible], 1-verso
    - Caracas Ven, Dargue, A call on U.S. Minister Cook, 2
    - Verso: Caracas Ven, Dargue, A call on U.S. Minister Cook, 2-verso
    - On the beach at Montevideo, 3
    - Verso: On the beach at Montevideo, 3-verso
    - Langley Field, Maj. Dargue, 4
    - Verso: Langley Field, Maj. Dargue, 4-verso
    - Langley Field, Maj. Dargue, 5
    - Verso: Langley Field, Maj. Dargue, 5-verso
    - Langley Field, Maj. Dargue, 6
    - Verso: Langley Field, Maj. Dargue, 6-verso
    - Help at Pocitos Beach Montevideo, 7
    - Verso: Help at Pocitos Beach Montevideo, 7-verso
    - Capt. Woolsey and the "Detroit"; Mrs. Woolsey Osborn Ohio, 8
    - Verso: Capt. Woolsey and the "Detroit"; Mrs. Woolsey Osborn Ohio, 8-verso
    - [Two Pan-American Flight planes], 9
    - [photograph of certificate presented to Major. H. A. Dargue from the President of Bolivia], 10
    - Puerto Cabello, 11
    - Verso: Puerto Cabello, 11-verso
    - Caracas Ven, Dargue, Placing a wreath at Tomb of Bolivar, 12
    - Verso: Caracas Ven, Dargue, Placing a wreath at Tomb of Bolivar, 12-verso
    - Caracas, Banquet at Military College[?], 13
    - Verso: Caracas, Banquet at Military College[?], 13-verso
    - Balloon with 21 flags of Pan American nations, May 2, 1927, 14
    - Verso: Balloon with 21 flags of Pan American nations, May 2, 1927, 14-verso
    - [U.S. Army Pan-American Fliers], 15
    - [Alter; taken during the Pan-American Flight], 16
    - [A large crowd of people; taken during the Pan-American Flight], 17
    - [A large group of people surrounding a ramp; taken during the Pan-American Flight], 18
    - [A large crowd of people going through a gate; taken during the Pan-American Flight], 19
    - [Broken wing of an airplane; taken during the Pan-American Flight], 20
    - [People surrounding a crashed plane in a vegetable field], 21
    - [People surrounding an automobile; taken during the Pan-American Flight], 22
    - [People surounding a crashed plane; taken during the Pan-American Flight], 23
    - Tegucigalpa, Honduras; Masonic Temple - completed 1915, 24
    - Verso: Tegucigalpa, Honduras; Masonic Temple - completed 1915, 24-verso
    - Islands, Gulf of Fonseca, 25
    - Verso: Islands, Gulf of Fonseca, 25-verso
    - Modern home in San Jose' - Costa Rica, 26
    - Verso: Modern home in San Jose' - Costa Rica, 26-verso
    - Cathedral - Costa Rica, 27
    - Verso: Cathedral - Costa Rica, 27-verso
    - Landing Field, San Jose, Costa Rica, 28
    - Verso: Landing Field, San Jose, Costa Rica, 28-verso
    - Landing Field at San Jose, C.R., 29
    - Verso: Landing Field at San Jose, C.R., 29-verso
    - Mount Misti from Arequipa, Peru, 30
    - Verso: Mount Misti from Arequipa, Peru, 30-verso
    - Indian Ruins, Peru, 31
    - Verso: Indian Ruins, Peru, 31-verso
    - Alpacas in Peru, 32
    - Verso: Alpacas in Peru, 32-verso
    - Capt. Woolsey, Photo from Mrs. Woolsey, 33
    - Verso: Capt. Woolsey, Photo from Mrs. Woolsey, 33-verso
  - Subject files: Pan America flight (United States Army), 1926 - 1927; 5 (Box 1552)
    - On Long Island Sound, 1
    - Verso: On Long Island Sound, 1-verso
    - Guatemala City, 2
    - Verso: Guatemala City, 2-verso
    - Forced landing of New York at Guatemala City, 3
    - Verso: Forced landing of New York at Guatemala City, 3-verso
    - Sperry Amphibian, 4
    - Verso: Sperry Amphibian, 4-verso
    - SUPERMARINE NAVEL AMPHIBIAN - BRITISH Showing the older type of amphibian with the dangerous position of the engine in reference to the pilot in case of a crash., 5
    - Verso: SUPERMARINE NAVEL AMPHIBIAN - BRITISH Showing the older type of amphibian with the dangerous position of the engine in reference to the pilot in case of a crash., 5-verso
    - With the Chief of Air Service in Montevideo, 6
    - Verso: With the Chief of Air Service in Montevideo, 6-verso
    - Landing in the surf at Montevideo, 7
    - Verso: Landing in the surf at Montevideo, 7-verso
    - Montevideo, 8
    - Verso: Montevideo, 8-verso
    - Leaving battleship at B/A to return to our planes, 9
    - Verso: Leaving battleship at B/A to return to our planes, 9-verso
    - In the harbor at B.A. [Buenos Aries], 10
    - Verso: In the harbor at B.A. [Buenos Aries], 10-verso
    - Just before the accident at B.A. [Buenos Aries], 11
    - Verso: Just before the accident at B.A. [Buenos Aries], 11-verso
    - The wreak of the New York, B.A., 12
    - Verso: The wreak of the New York, B.A., 12-verso
    - [Pan-American Flight plane], 13
    - [Pan-American Flight plane], 14
    - [Pan-American Flight plane being hauled out of the water by a crane], 15
    - [Two Pan-American Flight planes on a field], 16
    - [Crowd of people standing outside a Pan-American Flight plane], 17
    - [Man standing on a Pan-American Flight plane in the water], 18
    - Flying along the jungle coast of Panama en route to Colombia, 19
    - Verso: Flying along the jungle coast of Panama en route to Colombia, 19-verso
    - Caption: Passing Gaillard Cut on the way to South America. "Pan American Flight", 20
    - At Panama, 21
    - Verso: At Panama, 21-verso
    - Esperanga - an overnight stop en route up the steep railway to Bogota, 22
    - Verso: Esperanga - an overnight stop en route up the steep railway to Bogota, 22-verso
    - On the Magdalena R. at Girard, Col., 23
    - Verso: On the Magdalena R. at Girard, Col., 23-verso
    - Cartagena, 24
    - Verso: Cartagena, 24-verso
    - Before the banquet at Guayaquil, Ecuador; Governor of Guayas Province sitting with Maj. Dargue, 25